betdevil.com 2016-03-16

# BetDevil.com : Privacy Statement

**_Privacy Policy_**

Privacy Policy © BetDevil.com, all rights reserved 

BetDevil.com reserves the right to amend these Privacy Policies at any time. Any such revision will be binding and effective immediately on posting of notification of such changes on the web site. 

**Information Collected**

In order to access the site, the user is required to complete a registration form. Therefore, registration forms may require you to give us contact information (name, email address, postal address etc.). 

BetDevil.com will not sell your details or share it with third parties. Though BetDevil.com may share aggregate demographic and other general information with its advertisers and partners, it will never include data identifying you personally. BetDevil.com does send emails if you request them; you have complete control over the emails you receive, and can subscribe and unsubscribe at any time on the site. BetDevil.com will not give your email address to others to send you mail. 

**Cookies**

The BetDevil.com site may use cookies to track the length of time you spend on the site, or to store frequently used user information to personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small file placed by a Web site on your computer's hard drive. This file has no information about you personally, but identifies your computer when you return to our site. A cookie placed by a particular Web site can be accessed by that same web site, and contains only information volunteered by the user, such as your name or company name, or an innocuous user identification number or domain address. You can disable the cookie settings on your Internet browser although this is likely to impair your ability to view the Site. 

**Information Automatically Logged**

BetDevil.com uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. 

**Security**

BetDevil.com receives personal data via online applications. These applications require private data and we therefore employ industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted browsers. 

As no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you transfer the data at your own risk. 

**Message Boards/Chat Rooms/Forums**

If you utilise a chat room or message board/forum operated by BetDevil.com, your use of those services is governed by the Terms and Conditions attaching to those services. If you choose to publish your email address or other personal data, you do so at your own risk. 

* * *
